Guide to the Kenneth J. Arrow Papers, 1921-2017 RL.00052
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Writings, 1950-2017
  - Books, 1958-2017; 2
    - Collected Papers of Kenneth J. Arrow: Volume 4, Economics of Information (Chinese), 1989 (Box 33)
      Paperback
    - Collected Papers of Kenneth J. Arrow: Volume 5, Production and Capital, 1985 (Box 33)
    - Economic Theory of Organizations, undated (Box 39)
    - Economics and Ethics, 2011-2012 (Box 39)
    - Education in a Research University, 1996 (Box 33)
      Stanford University Press
    - Egyensúly és Döntés, 1979 (Box 33)
      Közgazdasági és Jogi Könyvkiadó, collection of Arrow's papers translated to Hungarian
    - Energy: the Next Twenty Years, 1979 (Box 33)
      Ballinger Publishing Company
    - Energy: The Next Twenty Years, 1976-1985; 3 folders (Box 39)
      Drafts, related correspondence
    - Energy: the Next Twenty Years, An Overview, 1979 (Box 33)
    - Equilibrio, incertezza, scelta sociale, 1987 (Box 33)
      Società editrice il Mulino, collection of Arrow's papers translated to Italian
    - Essays in the Theory of Risk-Bearing, 1971 (Box 33)
      North-Holland
    - Essays in the Theory of Risk-Bearing (Polish), 1979 (Box 33)
    - Frontiers of Economics, 1985 (Box 33)
      Basil Blackwell
    - General Competitive Analysis, 1971 (Box 33)
      Holden-Day, Inc.
    - General Competitive Analysis (Japanese), 1971 (Box 33)
      Iwanami Shoten Publishers
    - Handbook of Mathematical Economics, 1976-1979; 3 folders (Box 41)
      Notes and correspondence related to edited volumes
    - Handbook of Mathematical Economics: Volume 1, 1985 (Box 33)
    - Handbook of Mathematical Economics: Volume 1, 1981 (Box 33)
      North-Holland, special edition
    - Handbook of Social Choice and Welfare, 1997-2010; 2 folders (Box 39)
    - Handbooks of Economics, 1979-2008; 11 folders (Box 41)
      Correspondence and files related to editing Handbooks of Economics series
    - Incontro con Kenneth J. Arrow, 2003 (Box 33)
      La Citta' Del Sole, Italian printing of conference on Arrow's work, text in English
    - Issues in Contemporary Economics, 1991 (Box 33)
      Macmillan
    - Landmark Papers in General Equilibrium Theory, 1999-2002 (Box 39)
    - Landmark Papers in General Equilibrium Theory, Social Choice and Welfare, 2001 (Box 33)
      Edward Elgar
    - Limits of Organization (German), 1980 (Box 33)
      Betriebswirtchaftlicher Verlag
    - Limits of Organization (Chinese), 2005 (Box 33)
      Note to Arrow on inside cover
    - Limits of Organization (French), 1976 (Box 33)
      Presses Universitaires de France
    - Limits of Organization (Japanese), 1974 (Box 33)
      Japan UNI Agency, note to Arrow on inside cover
    - Limits of Organization (Polish), 1985 (Box 34)
      Pa?stwowe Wydawnictwo Naukowe
    - Meritocracy and Economic Inequality, 2000 (Box 34)
      Princeton University Press
    - Obra de Kenneth Arrow: Una Selección, 2014 (Box 34)
      Ministerio de Hacienda Y Administraciones Públicas, collection of Arrow's papers translated to Spanish
    - On Ethics and Economics: Conversations with Kenneth J. Arrow, 2017 (Box 34)
      Routledge
    - On Ethics and Economics: Conversations with Kenneth J. Arrow, 2017 (Box 34)
      Routledge, paperback
    - Petroleum Price Regulation, 1979 (Box 34)
      American Enterprise Institute for Public Policy Research
    - Public Investment, the Rate of Return, and Optimal Fiscal Policy, 1970 (Box 34)
      Johns Hopkins University Press on behalf of Resources for the Future
    - Rational Foundations of Economic Behaviour, 1996 (Box 34)
    - Rational Foundations of Economic Behaviour, 1999 (Box 34)
      Macmillan Press, paperback
    - Readings in Welfare Economics, 1969 (Box 34)
      George Allen and Unwin
    - Readings in Welfare Economics, 1969 (Box 34)
      Richard D. Irwin, Inc., inscription on inside cover
    - Saving Lives, Buying Time: Economics of Malaria Drugs in an Age of Resistance, 2004 (Box 34)
      Institute of Medicine, National Academic Press
    - Saving Lives, Buying Time: Economics of Malaria Drugs in an Age of Resistance (Executive Summary), 2004 (Box 34)
    - Selected Readings in Economic Theory from Econometrica, 1971 (Box 34)
      MIT Press
    - Social Choice and Individual Values (Chinese), undated (Box 34)
    - Social Choice and Individual Values (Chinese), 2010 (Box 34)
    - Social Choice and Individual Values (Chinese), 2010 (Box 34)
    - Social Choice and Individual Values: 1st edition (Spanish), 1994 (Box 34)
      Planeta-Agostini
    - Social Choice and Individual Values: 2nd Edition, 1963 (Box 34)
      Yale University Press, Cowles Foundation Monograph printing
    - Social Choice and Individual Values: 2nd Edition, 1963 (Box 34)
      Yale University Press, paperback
    - Social Choice and Individual Values: 2nd edition (French), 1997 (Box 34)
      Diderot Éditeur
    - Social Choice and Individual Values: 2nd edition (Italian, second edition), 2003 (Box 34)
      Etas
    - Social Choice and Individual Values: 2nd edition (Korean), 1988 (Box 34)
      Korea Economic Daily
    - Social Choice and Individual Values: 2nd edition (Russian), 2004 (Box 34)
    - Social Choice and Individual Values: 3rd Edition, 2012 (Box 34)
      Yale University Press
    - Social Choice and Multicriterion Decision-Making, 1986 (Box 34)
    - Social Choice and Multicriterion Decision-Making, 1979-1990; 3 folders (Box 39)
      Drafts, proofs, related correspondence
    - Social Choice and Multicriterion Decision-Making (Spanish), 1989 (Box 34)
      Alianza Editorial
    - Social Choice: Many Individuals or Many Criteria, 2000 (Box 34)
      Yale University Press, international printing
    - Social Choice: Many Individuals or Many Criteria (Chinese), 2000 (Box 34)
    - Studies in Applied Probability and Management Science, 1962 (Box 34)
    - Studies in Linear and Non-Linear Programming, 1958 (Box 34)
      Stanford University Press, paperback
    - Studies in Linear and Non-Linear Programming, 1958 (Box 35)
    - Studies in Linear and Non-Linear Programming (Russian), 1962 (Box 34)
    - Studies in Resource Allocation Processes, 1977 (Box 35)
      Cambridge University Press
    - Studies in Resource Allocation Processes, 1977 (Box 35)
      Cambridge University Press, paperback
    - Studies in the Mathematical Theory of Inventory and Production, 1958 (Box 35)
      Stanford University Press, autographed
    - Théorie de l'Information et des organisations, 2000 (Box 35)
      Dunod, collection of Arrow's papers translated to French
    - Time Series Analysis of Inter-industry Demands, 1959 (Box 35)
    - What Does the Present Owe the Future: An Economic and Ethical Perspective on Climate Changes, 1996 (Box 35)
      Grace A. Tanner Center for Human Values, published version of Tanner Lecture
  - Festschrifts, 1976-2008; 3
    Contains documents for Arrow's contributions to festschrift volumes in honor of other scholars.
    - Alchain Tribute, 2001 (Box 36)
    - Arrow Festschrift, undated (Box 36)
      Draft invite list
    - Beckman Festschrift, 1983 (Box 36)
      Related correspondence
    - Bergson Festschrift, 1981-1982 (Box 36)
    - Black Festschrift, 1986-1988 (Box 36)
    - Borch Festschrift, 1988 (Box 36)
    - Ehrlich Festschrift, 1980-1983 (Box 36)
    - Fitoussi Festschrift, 2002 (Box 36)
      Original, presentation slides
    - Galbraith Festschrift, 1987-1989 (Box 36)
    - Hahn Festschrift, 1990-1991 (Box 36)
      Proofs, drafts, related correspondence
    - Harcourt Preface, 1994-1997 (Box 36)
    - Harsanyi Festschrift, 1990-1991 (Box 36)
    - Hotelling Festschrift, 1988 (Box 36)
    - Houthakker, Henk Festschrift, 1990-1991 (Box 36)
    - Hurwicz Festschrift, 1981-1987 (Box 36)
    - Kantovich Festschrift, 1987 (Box 36)
    - Karlin Festschrift, 1988 (Box 36)
      Proofs, drafts
    - Krutilla Festschrift, 1984-1985 (Box 36)
    - Labini, Sylos Festschrift, 1990 (Box 36)
    - Lerner Festschrift, 1976-1978 (Box 36)
    - Lieberman Festschrift, 1994-1996 (Box 36)
      Related files and correspondence
    - Lieberman Paper, 1998 (Box 36)
      Proofs, related correspondence
    - Lipinski Festschrift, 1978-1979 (Box 36)
    - Reder Festschrift, 1983-1984 (Box 36)
    - Robinson Festschrift, 1984-1986 (Box 36)
    - Schelling Fest, 2008 (Box 36)
    - Sen Festschrift, 1990-1994 (Box 36)
    - Shubik Festschrift, 1991 (Box 36)
    - Simon Memorial, 2003 (Box 36)
    - Stiglitz Festschrift, 2002 (Box 36)
    - Suppes Festschrift, 1991 (Box 36)
    - Suzumura Fest, 2004 (Box 36)
    - Tversky Memorial, 1997 (Box 36)
    - Vickery Papers, 1988-1993 (Box 36)
    - Von Neumann Festschrift, 1986-1988 (Box 36)
    - Williamson 70th, 2002-2003 (Box 36)
    - Williamson Conference, 1996 (Box 36)
  - Referee Reports, 1977-2011; 4
    Contains documents for Arrow's activities as a referee for many academic journals and publishers.
    - FEEM/Elgar, 2003-2011 (Box 36)
      Referee reports for book series
    - NAS-Minelli Polemarchakis, 1999 (Box 36)
      Referee files for report for Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences
    - New Palgrave, 2002-2004 (Box 36)
      Referee reports for New Palgrave Dictionary of Economics
    - Referee Reports: A-C, 1977-2004 (Box 36)
    - Referee Reports: D-F, 1978-2003 (Box 36)
    - Referee Reports: G-J, 1979-2008 (Box 36)
    - Referee Reports: K-R, 1979-2004 (Box 36)
    - Referee Reports: S, 1984-2008 (Box 36)
    - Referee Reports: T-Z, 1983-2005 (Box 36)
    - Referee Reports electronic records, 1999-2016; 21 files; 5 MB. (Digital-materials RL00052-SET-0003)
    - Referees: Requests, 1980-2001 (Box 36)
- Academia, 1948-2017
  Includes teaching materials, committee, consulting, volunteer, and other work for Arrow's professorships at Stanford, Harvard, and the Santa Fe Institute.
  - Stanford University, 1948-2017; 1
    Contains documents for committee service, teaching, and departmental duties from Arrow's time at Stanford.
    - ECON 185: Distribution of Income & Wealth, 1978-1995; 8 folders (Box 64)
      Teaching notes and course readers
    - ECON 186: Ethics of Social Decisions, 1987-1993; 2 folders (Box 64)
      Teaching notes and course reader
    - ECON 200: History of Economic Thought, 1983-1994; 2 folders (Box 64)
      Teaching notes
    - ECON 202: General Equilibrium Talk, 2003-2015; 2 folders (Box 64)
      Materials for guest lecture in graduate microeconomics course
    - ECON 203: Price and Allocation Theory II, 1980-1982; 3 folders (Box 64)
    - ECON 203: Price and Allocation Theory II, 1980-1982 (Box 65)
    - ECON 205: Price Allocation Theory, undated (Box 65)
    - ECON 215: The Theory of Competitive Equilibrium, 1967 (Box 65)
    - ECON 280, 1982-1983 (Box 65)
    - ECON 282: Theory of Information and Organization, 1971-1996; 13 folders (Box 65)
      Teaching notes, reserve lists, problem sets, and course reader
    - ECON 386: Interdisciplinary Seminar on Conflict Resolution, 1981-1993 (Box 65)
      Teaching notes, flyers, and related correspondence
    - ECON 388: Interdisciplinary Seminar on Risk Management, 1989-1990; 2 folders (Box 65)
      Seminar papers and flyers
    - Micro Econ XX, undated (Box 65)
    - Optimal Growth Lectures, 1967 (Box 65)
    - Statistics Exam, 1948-1966 (Box 65)
      Exams
    - Teaching Notes, 1982 (Box 65)
      Unlabeled teaching notes
    - Theories of Economic Justice, undated (Box 65)
      Seminar notes
    - Alternative Approaches, 1986-1988 (Box 65)
      Files for search in Alternative Approaches area
    - Bresnahan Review, 1981-1986 (Box 65)
      Files for faculty member review
    - Building, 1991 (Box 65)
      Files related to building for Economics Department
    - Cogan Appointment, 1982-1984 (Box 65)
      Files for faculty hiring
    - COGEE, 1996 (Box 65)
    - Dasgupta Appointment, 1988 (Box 65)
    - Department Computer, 1988 (Box 65)
      Instruction files for department computer system
    - Economics Department, 1983-1985 (Box 65)
      Department meeting files
    - Economics Department, 1967-2004; 4 folders (Box 66)
    - Engineering Research Center, 1985 (Box 66)
    - Environmental Economics, 1990-1992; 2 folders (Box 66)
    - Environment Program, 2003 (Box 66)
      Course listings
    - Ethics in Society, 1985-1993; 13 folders (Box 66)
      Files for Ethics in Society program
    - Expense Reports, 2007-2010; 2 folders (Box 66)
    - Extradepartment Education (ED), 1981-1985; 13 folders (Box 66)
      Files for extradepartmental education committee
    - Faculty Committee on Research, 1992 (Box 66)
    - Faculty Report, 1983-1984 (Box 66)
      Reports on faculty research activity
    - Gardner Fellowship, 1985-1989 (Box 66)
      Files for serving as selection committee chair
    - Health and Safety, 1987-1990; 4 folders (Box 67)
      Files for health and safety committee
    - Homeowner's Governance, 1989 (Box 67)
      Files for campus homeowners association
    - Hoover Institution, 1981-1994; 3 folders (Box 67)
    - Housing, 1981-1983 (Box 67)
    - Humanities Center, 1983-1991 (Box 67)
    - Humanities & Sciences Council, 1986 (Box 67)
    - Japan Trade Studies, 1985 (Box 67)
    - Job Market, 1979 (Box 67)
      Received letters recommending candidates for a faculty position
    - Kornai Appointment, 1985 (Box 67)
    - Mathematical Sciences Education, 1994-1985 (Box 67)
      Files for serving on board of Center for Research in Mathematical Sciences Education
    - Medical Non-Tenure, 1986-1987 (Box 67)
      Files for serving on committee to expand non-tenure stream medical school faculty
    - Memos, 1988 (Box 67)
    - Misc. Department Files, 2011-2017 (Box 67)
    - Operations Research, 1990-1991 (Box 67)
      Files for department meetings
    - Patent Agreement Contract Misc., 1979 (Box 67)
    - Payroll Info, 1979 (Box 67)
    - Political Economics, 1985-1986 (Box 67)
      Files for doctoral program in political economics
    - Public Service Requirement, 1990 (Box 67)
    - Reagan Library, 1986 (Box 67)
      Files related to controversy over proposed Reagan Library at Stanford
    - Research Administration Information, 1999 (Box 67)
    - Research Committee, 1992 (Box 67)
    - Seltzer, Leon E., 1988 (Box 67)
      Files for establishing endowed book fund
    - Seminars, 1979-1983 (Box 67)
      Seminar papers
    - South Africa, 1986 (Box 67)
      Files related to proposed disinvestment in South Africa
    - Stanford Retreat, 1990 (Box 67)
    - Stanford Senate, 1987-1989; 2 folders (Box 67)
      Files for chairing faculty senate
    - Stanford Senate: Western Culture, 1985-1988; 3 folders (Box 67)
    - Stanford Summer, 1979 (Box 67)
      Files for summer seminar
    - SUPER - SU Project for Environmental Research, 1990 (Box 67)
    - Suspense, 2012-2013 (Box 67)
      Files for expense reimbursement
    - TSEMI, 1991 (Box 67)
    - Visiting Scholars, 1986 (Box 67)
    - Alumni, 1985-1987 (Box 67)
    - Arora Project, 2012 (Box 67)
    - Bakersfield, 1987 (Box 67)
      Alumni files
    - Centennial Campaign, 1986-1989 (Box 67)
    - Entering Student Talk, 1983 (Box 67)
    - Football Recruiting, 1990 (Box 67)
    - Fundamental Standard, 1989 (Box 67)
      Stanford Speech Code
    - Grant Files, 1997 (Box 67)
    - Ground Rent Task Force, 1988-1989 (Box 68)
      Files related to Stanford Homeowners Association
    - Harvard Overseers, 1986-1994 (Box 68)
      Files for serving on external review committee for Economics Department at Harvard University
    - Karlin Memorial Resolution, 2007 (Box 68)
    - Manne Memorial Resolution, 2009 (Box 68)
    - Misc. University Files, 1994 (Box 68)
    - Population Studies, undated (Box 68)
    - RDCEP (Robust Decision Making on Climate and Economic Policy), 2013 (Box 68)
      Files related to serving on external review committee for center at University of Chicago
    - Stanford Appointment, 1974-1979; 2 folders (Box 68)
      Files for negotiating return to Stanford
    - Stanford electronic records, 2006-2017; 39 files; approximately 18 MB. (Digital-materials RL00052-SET-0003)
    - Stanford - New York, 1983 (Box 68)
    - Stanford Pioneers, 2009 (Box 68)
    - Sterling Resolution, 1985 (Box 68)
    - Yale Visiting Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 68)
      Files related to external review of Economics Department at Yale University
  - Harvard University, 1966-1993; 2
    Contains documents for committee service, teaching, and departmental duties for Arrow's time at Harvard.
    - ECON 225: Seminar in Production Functions, 1968 (Box 68)
      Teaching materials and files for course design
    - Economics 2010a, 1973 (Box 68)
      Teaching notes and reading list
    - Economics 2181: Economics of Information, 1975-1979; 3 folders (Box 68)
      Teaching notes, course materials, and exams
    - Liquidity Preference, undated (Box 68)
      Lecture notes
    - Arrow - Dead Files (Harvard Move), 1966-1967 (Box 68)
    - Department of Economics, 1974-1977 (Box 68)
      Files for department business
    - Department of Economics: Faculty Appointments, 1989-1993 (Box 68)
    - Department of Economics: Macroeconomics Search, 1971 (Box 68)
    - Harvard Audit, 1981 (Box 68)
      Files related to review of grant-funded projects at Harvard
    - Harvard Faculty Council, 1976; 2 folders (Box 68)
    - Harvard Miscellaneous, 1974-1979 (Box 68)
    - Wells Prize, 1978 (Box 68)
      Files related to dissertation prize selection
    - Board of Syndics, 1975-1978 (Box 68)
    - Divestiture - South Africa, 1979 (Box 68)
    - Houses, 1970-1974 (Box 68)
    - International Studies Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 68)
    - Kirkland House, 1974-1979 (Box 68)
    - Visitation Committee for Graduate Program Review - UMass Amherst, 1978 (Box 68)
      Files for external review of graduate program in economics at University of Massachusetts - Amherst
    - Women - Hiring Practices, 1975 (Box 68)
      Files related to Equal Employment Opportunity hiring
    - References Correspondence, 1968-1979; 22 folders (Box 69)
      Letters of recommendation
  - Santa Fe Institute, 1987-2015; 3
    Includes documents from Arrow's work at the Santa Fe Institute, including work on program boards, research initiatives, and Institute workshops.
    - Santa Fe Institute (SFI), 1987-2008; 2 folders (Box 68)
      Files for Institute business
    - Climate Change, 1997 (Box 70)
    - Complexity, 1993 (Box 70)
      Files for serving on editorial board of Institute journal
    - Economics Board, 1991-2001; 2 folders (Box 70)
      Files for serving on board of economics program at Institute
    - Economics Program, 1987-2001; 13 folders (Box 70)
    - Editorial Board, 1989-1993 (Box 70)
    - Evolving III, 2001 (Box 70)
      Files for Institute workshop
    - External Professorship, 1988-1993 (Box 70)
      Files for accepting external professorship at Institute
    - Farmer Appointment, 1999 (Box 70)
      Files for hiring
    - Fund Raising, 1989-1990 (Box 70)
    - Global Security, 1989 (Box 70)
    - Hahn, 1988 (Box 70)
      Correspondence related to Frank Hahn's visit to Institute
    - Information and Games, 2012 (Box 70)
    - Integrative Themes, undated (Box 70)
      Hand-written notes
    - Journal, 1990 (Box 70)
      Files for establishing Institute journal
    - Kaufman, 1998 (Box 70)
      Files discussing potential conflicts of interest
    - Keck Advisory Committee, 1998-2000 (Box 70)
    - Learning Initiative, 1996 (Box 70)
      Files related to initiative at NSF
    - Limits to Knowledge, 1996 (Box 70)
      Files for Institute conference
    - Makoto, 2001 (Box 70)
      Files for serving on advisory board of postdoctoral program
    - Misc., 1986-1987 (Box 70)
    - November Visit, 1988 (Box 70)
    - Pines on University, 1998 (Box 70)
      Correspondence on rethinking the university system
    - Poverty Trap Workshop, 2000-2001 (Box 70)
    - Presidential Search, 1990 (Box 70)
    - Publications, 1988-1990 (Box 70)
    - Rand Collaboration, 1991 (Box 70)
    - Risk, 2009 (Box 70)
      Files for risk initiative at Institute
    - Sage Proposal, 1990 (Box 70)
      Files for grant proposal with Russell Sage Foundation
    - Santa Fe Institute electronic records, 2005-2014; 5 files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00052-SET-0003)
    - Short Course, 2012 (Box 70)
    - Science Board, 1988-2015; 4 folders (Box 70)
      Files from serving on board
    - Social Interactions, 1996-1999 (Box 70)
    - Social Robustness, 2002-2003 (Box 70)
      Files for Institute meeting
    - Summer School, 1988-1992 (Box 71)
    - Systemic Risk, 2009 (Box 71)
      Files for Systemic Risk Initiative
    - Workshop, 1987-1989; 3 folders (Box 71)
    - Workshop - Complex Adaptive Systems, 1992 (Box 71)
    - Workshop - Growth and Cities, 1991 (Box 71)
    - Workshop - Increasing Returns, 1992 (Box 71)
    - Workshop - Organizational Learning, 1993 (Box 71)
- Personal Materials, 1921-2017
  Comprised of the Awards and Honorary Degrees Subseries, which includes the John Bates Clark Medal, the John von Neumann Theory Prize, the National Medal of Science, and the Nobel Prize, as well as honorary degree certificates and accompanying logistical information surrounding those ceremonies; as well as the Personal Items Subseries, which contains biographical material, photographs, scrapbooks, travel journals, datebooks, rolodexes, news clippings, and other materials.
  - Awards and Honorary Degrees, 1
    Contains Arrow's awards and honorary degrees, including the John Bates Clark Medal, the John von Neumann Theory Prize, the National Medal of Science, and the Nobel Prize, in addition to honorary degrees and certificates from various institutions.
    - American Nobel, 1990 (Box 74)
    - APSA - Lippincott, 2009 (Box 74)
    - Awards and Honorary Degrees electronic records, 2009-2011; 2 files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00052-SET-0003)
    - Cambridge Degree, 1985 (Box 74)
    - Churchill College, 1988-2013 (Box 74)
    - General Awards, 1951-2013 (Box 75)
      Includes a variety of awards and certificates
    - General Awards, 1986-2009 (Box 79)
      Includes various awards
    - General Awards and Certificates, 1956-2015 (Box 78)
      Includes various awards and recognitions
    - GFA Award, 1982 (Box 74)
    - Harvard Degree, 1998-1999 (Box 74)
    - Honorary Degrees, 1994-2012 (Box 75)
      Includes honorary degrees from various institutions
    - Honorary Degrees, Awards, 1971-2009; 3 folders (Box 76)
      Includes various honorary degrees and awards
    - International Award of the Indian Econometric Society, 1975 (Box 74)
    - Jewish Hall of Fame, 1976-1989 (Box 74)
    - John Bates Clark Award, 1957; 1 medal (Box 92)
    - John von Neumann Theory Prize, 1986 (Box 78)
    - John von Neumann Theory Prize, 1986; 1 medal (Box 92)
    - Monash University, 2003-2007 (Box 74)
    - National Medal of Science, 2005-2006 (Box 74)
    - National Medal of Science, 2004; 1 medal (Box 92)
    - Nobel Award Ceremonies, 1972; 2 folders (Box 74)
    - Nobel Jubilee, 1991 (Box 74)
    - Nobel diploma, 1972 (Box 94)
    - Nobel Prize, 1972; 1 medal (Box 93)
    - Photo Album from Hebrew University of Jerusalem, 1975 (Box 84)
      Includes photos and materials from honorary doctorate ceremony and celebration
    - Photo Album from Chinese University of Hong Kong, 2008 (Box 83)
      Includes photos from Sun Hung Kai Nobel Laureates Distinguished Lectures
    - Photo Album from Tel Aviv University, 2001 (Box 84)
    - Royal Academy of Sciences, 1973 (Box 74)
    - Sacro Cuore Degree, 1994 (Box 74)
    - Sigma Phi Epsilon, 1986 (Box 74)
    - Sigma Xi, 1982; 2 folders (Box 74)
    - Tel Aviv University, 2001 (Box 74)
    - Townsend Harris Alumni Association, 1980-1991 (Box 74)
    - Uppsala Degrees, 1994 (Box 74)
    - Vienna Budapest Romania, 2011-2013 (Box 74)